forexintrade.com 2019-05-14

# Privacy Policy – Forexintrade – Forex Trading

Who are we  
The address of our website is: http://forexintrade.com.

What personal information do you collect on what day  
Comments  
We also collect IP address and browser information text.

A text (also called a hash) that has generated your email address can be provided to the Gravatar service, ready to use. The privacy policy of the Gravatar service is as follows: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After your comment is confirmed, everyone will appear with your profile photo comment.

Environment  
If your images are web based, it is inevitable to identify them with embedded locations (EXIF GPS). Website addressers download and present one of the things on your website.

Contact forms  
Cookies  
It does not create a comment on my site, it does so by storing your name, email address, and web site in cookies. They are great for convenience, you can leave them somewhere else. These materials stay for a year.

If you have an account and log in to this site, we will accept your browser code. This cookie contains no personal data and closes your browser.

If you log in, thank you for logging in and your screen display selection. Entry layouts display for one day. If you select the option “Remember me”, your entry will continue for two weeks. If you sign out of your account, the login cookies are removed.

You can make a cookie or add an additional cookie to your browser. This description shows the personal identity of the article with no personal verification and only the edited article. Time goes by after 1 day.

Related content from other sites  
Articles on this site may contain embedded content (e.g., videos, images, articles, etc.). Other web programs behave in a fully functioning way of obtaining information on the internet.

The content of this site allows you to have a page, a content, and a website.

Analysis  
Who do you share your verse  
How long do you keep your data  
A comment ortayaving, comments and metadata are kept indefinitely. We will inspect and approve the assembly to check your subsequent comments.

You have personal information to register with my website. All puzzles can be personalized, edited or edited (except for username change). Web site administrators can also stamp and edit this information.

Your data Your microphone rights  
If you have an account of this account, whether it is united or not, I got it from one side. You may also want to delete all personal computers as well. This is not appropriate for administrative, legal, and purposeful purposes.

Where do you send your data  
Automatic commenting is possible.

Contact  
Additional info  
How do we protect your data  
What data breach procedures do we have  
Which third parties are using data  
What kind of automatic decision making and / or profiling are we in terms of the user?  
Obligation of illumination of the Ministry of Industry
